(Howard:)No, I don't know
his immigration status.
Relax, I'm still on hold!
(Howard:)Speaking.
(Howard:)Okay, sure,
I can meet with you on Thursday.
(Howard:)Caltech is fine.
(Howard:)Yeah, and may I ask
what this is about?
(Howard:)I may not?
(Raj:)That's what he said to me.
(Leonard:)Here you are, Mother.
(Beverley:)Thank you.
(Leonard:)I'm glad you decided to stay.
(Leonard:)It's gonna be special for Penny
and me to share this with you.
(Penny:)I can't wait
for this day to be over.
(Leonard:)Yeah, special, like that.
(Leonard:)That's them.
(Leonard:)Please don't make things
(Leonard:)any more awkward
than they already are.
(Sheldon:)All right, so less
or equally awkward, got it.
(Leonard:)Hey, guys, come on in.
(Alfred:)Oh, thank you.
Good morning.
(Mary:)Morning.
Hello.